never transferred to its respective doomed flight, which, when searched, just so happened
to contain written-app breakdowns of all 19 hijackers, their backgrounds, their motives,
each of their assignments, their ties to al-Qaeda, a video cassette of a Boeing flight simulator,
a knife and pepper spray.
The entire plot of 9-11 neatly packaged and dropped in their lap of all the passengers
and all the planes, the one suitcase that just so happened to not make the plane has
a written-app breakdown of the attacks.
I call this one the magic suitcase, which when coupled with the magic passports, you get
the FBI's official reasoning when asked how on earth they were instantly able to discern
all of the hijackers and how they were attached to al-Qaeda.
That is some stroke of luck.